SHRADDHA PANDE

Software Developer

PROFILE SUMMARY:

A Software Engineer having ~2 years of experience in Application Development and enhancement who has worked in agile practices and having knowledge of Object-Oriented Programming with Python, C++ and well conversant with the concepts of Core Java, JavaScript.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HCL(Transitioned as a part of Strategic parternship between DELL-HCL)

Apr 2021- Present

DELL EMC - Pune, MH

Software Engineer - Sept 2019 - March 2021

Product: Data Protection Advisor (DPA)

A Platform for performing reporting and analytics on a data protection environment. This solution can monitor technologies including backup software, storage array replication, servers, databases, and virtual infrastructures. Contribution-

- Enhanced the existing data collection requests to collect the information from DPA-supported backup and storage software.
- Worked on improving the Report engine interactions via REST APIs
- Converted the configuration of global settings for Reports form FLEX to HTML
- Provided fixes, workarounds for various customer escalations
- Involved in customer interactions understanding the requirements and interacting across the teams for demonstrations

Technologies Used: Python, C++, JavaScript

Symantec Software - Pune, MH

Intern - Jan 2019- June 2019

Product: Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR)

A Plugin to the EDR which visualizes threats and gives detailed overview of what sequence of activities have occurred in the current system/network which caused threat. An EDR dashboard will track, analyze, and display the status of the system with the help of various graphs, charts, and timelines.

Technologies Used: Java, JavaScript, Elasticsearch, Kibana, AngularJS

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Crop Prediction Using Machine Learning and IOT

An application which uses machine learning techniques for classification, applied to Data responsible to predict the type of crop can grow in the field. Technologies used: Java, Python, Machine Learning, IoT

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Applications (MCA) -2019 Vishwakarma Institute of Technology - Pune, MH

Post Graduated with 82.71%

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCS) -2016 H.P.T. Arts & R.Y.K. Science College - Nashik, MH

Graduated with 67.42%

Pune, Maharashtra



9403773955



shraddha.p.pande@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/shraddha-pande



https://github.com/shraddhapp

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages:

Python, C++, Core Java, JavaScript. HTML.CSS

Databases:

SQL, Elasticsearch

Tools and IDEs: VS Code, Eclipse

Version Control Systems: GitHub, Bitbucket

ACHIEVEMENTS AND EXTRACURRICULAR

- Awarded with 'Best Outgoing Student' of VIT, 2019.
- Project leader on multiple assignments during post-graduation.
- Winner of Blind coding competition held at VIT, Pune.
- Attended a workshop on "Machine Learning and Data Analytics using Python" held at VIT, Pune.
- Participation in hackathons.
- Member of various ERGs and CSR activities in DELL.